(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
宝鐘マリン 生誕祭LIVE
-新衣装お披露目-
重大告知あり！ 3D新衣装！？
Houshou Marine Birthday Live
-New Outfit Reveal-
Big Announcement! 3D New Outfit!?
Unison
片時も　大好きなのに　勘繰るわ
I'm in love with you every moment, yet I'm suspicious.
潜っただけ　淡いか　延命した
Just dove in, is it faint? I prolonged my life.
可愛いわ　延命した
It's cute, I prolonged my life.
可愛いな
How cute.
波の上　拾いものも中毒さ
Even things picked up on the waves are addictive.
広い空だのに奇妙な予感だ
Despite the wide sky, I have a strange premonition.
そうか　カンだ
I see, it was a hunch.
船長を決めてなかったんだ
We hadn't decided on a captain.
それがじゃんけん　先を急いだんだ
That was rock-paper-scissors, I was in a hurry.
視線今強引な
A forceful gaze now.
頬は紅潮で全員さ
Everyone's cheeks are flushed.
他人に不用邸だ
I'm a useless manor to others.
口をしまい開錠だ
Shut your mouth, it's unlocked.
奪い合いなら解錠だ
If it's a scramble, then it's unlocked.
助けてすっかり遭難
Help, I'm completely shipwrecked.
みんな自分に入れるかどうか
Whether everyone will let me in.
というわけでサイレンス　気にしないんだ
So, silence, I don't care.
誰にしたって気にしない　最後の航海だ
I don't care who it is, it's the final voyage.
からきし笑い方
A completely hopeless way of laughing.
さあ舵を取って交代だ
Now, take the helm and change shifts.
どうしてさ　見渡して
Why? Look around.
どうして　どうして
Why? Why?
比べるのが意味じゃない
Comparing is not the point.
いいな
It's nice.
みんな
Everyone.
お願い、choose me
Please, choose me.
ほら　早く、今日中に
Look, hurry, by the end of today.
お願い、choose me
Please, choose me.
君が今日選んでくれないと　なんもできない
If you don't choose me today, I can't do anything.
考えてくれないと　心配に感じちゃうんだ
If you don't think about it, I'll start to feel worried.
こんなとこで迷ってると　沈むよ、深海に
If you hesitate here, you'll sink into the deep sea.
沈むよ、深海に
You'll sink into the deep sea.
濡れてきた　震える体　溢れてきちゃった
I've gotten wet, my shivering body, it's overflowing.
船底から穴が空いた　今
A hole has opened in the bottom of the ship, now.
座礁して　どうして
Running aground, why?
直せるのが君じゃない？
Why isn't it you who can fix it?
いいな
It's nice.
みんな
Everyone.
お願い、修理
Please, repair me.
さあ、ほら今すぐに
Now, look, right now.
塞いで熱中して
Block it up and get absorbed.
熱中して！
Get absorbed!
君が今日塞いでくれないと　なんもできない
If you don't block it up today, I can't do anything.
信じてる
Believe...
そろそろ限界値
Almost at the limit
大事なもの探しに行かない？
Shall we go look for something important?
偉大な夢の旅、異世界に
A journey of grand dreams, in another world
君がいないと意味なんてない
Without you, it's meaningless
考えてくれないと心配に
I worry if you don't think about it
感じちゃうんだ こんなとこで
I start to feel it in a place like this
迷ってると行けないよ、絶対に
If you're lost, you'll never make it, for sure
行けないよ、絶対に
Never make it, for sure
マリン出航！！
Marine Shukkou!!
作詞：砂守岳央 作曲：田中公平
Lyrics: Sunamori Takeo, Composition: Tanaka Kohei
世界が壊れてゆく
The world is falling apart
泣き声が聞こえていた
I could hear the crying voices
汚れた拳 痛むほど
Clenching my dirty fist so hard it hurt
強く握った
I held on tight
当たり前に笑ってた昨日はもうどこにもない
The yesterday where we laughed normally is nowhere to be found
明日がどんな日になるのか
No one knows what kind of day tomorrow will be
誰も知らない
No one knows
正義にさえ捨てられた今日
I swear to take back today
取り戻すことを
which was abandoned even by justice
誓う
I swear
錨上げ！
Anchor's aweigh!
勇気の旗上げて
Raise the flag of courage
旅立とう 嵐の海
And set sail into the stormy sea
立ち上がれ
Stand up
幸せは願えば
Happiness isn't cheap enough
手に入るほど安くはない
to get just by wishing
守るために戦うなら
If you're going to fight to protect
海賊に なればいい
Then just become a pirate
幸せ 簡単に
Happiness easily
掌の中消えてしまう
disappears from within one's palm
悲劇をただ見てることが
If you can't forgive just watching
許せないなら
the tragedy unfold
一人きりで震えていた昨日はもう消えはしない
The yesterday where you trembled alone will never disappear
それでも決意 胸に抱けば
But if you hold your determination in your heart
もう迷わない
You will no longer hesitate
道半ばで倒れた友に
Embracing the words entrusted
託された言葉
by friends who fell halfway
抱き
And hold them tight
錨上げ！
Anchor's aweigh!
自由の旗上げて
Raise the flag of freedom
突き進め 大海原
And push forward through the vast ocean
燃え上がれ
Blaze up
どんな雨だろうとも
Become a flame that never goes out
消えることなき 炎になれ
no matter what rain falls
錨上げ！
Anchor's aweigh!
勇気の旗上げて
Raise the flag of courage
旅立とう 嵐の海
And set sail into the stormy sea
立ち上がれ
Stand up
幸せは願えば
Happiness isn't cheap enough
手に入るほど安くはない
to get just by wishing
守るために戦うなら
If you're going to fight to protect
海賊に なればいい
Then just become a pirate
ハロヘヨホホホ
Halohe Yohohoho
ヨホホホハロヘ
Yohohoho Halohe
ホホヘイ
Hohohei
ヨホヘイ
Yohohei
ヨホホホハロヘ
Yohohoho Halohe
恐れずにここで
Without fear, stand up here
夜明けの向こう側の果てに
at the end beyond the dawn
立ち上がれ
And stand tall
ヨホホホハロヘ
Yohohoho Halohe
ホホヘイ
Hohohei
ヨホヘイ
Yohohei
一人きりいつか
Alone someday, if we gather
集まればやがて
eventually a great pirate crew
偉大なる海賊団
A grand fleet of pirates
錨上げ！
Anchor's aweigh!
出航！！
Set sail!!
はい、ということで、まず2曲聴いていただきました。
All right! So we just heard the first two songs.
はい、本日は何の日？そう、宝鐘マリンお誕生日です！
Yes! What day is it today? That's right! It's Houshou Marine's birthday!
はい、今日のハッシュタグは #宝鐘マリン生誕祭2022 まなんですけど、
Yes! Today's hashtag is #HoushouMarineBirthdayFest2022, but...
ま、今日はね、何といっても、ま、ここに書いてある通り、え、3Dのね、新衣装のお披露目もあります！
well, today, more than anything, as written here, we also have the 3D new costume reveal!
もうこれはね、隠しておくのは無理なんで先に言っちゃいます。でもう隠してることもひとつあるのよな。
It's impossible to keep it hidden anymore, so I'm just saying it now. And there's one more thing I'm hiding...
ちょっと隠してることも、え、終盤にね、お披露目したいと思いますので最後までしっかり見てください。
I'll reveal that hidden thing at the end, so please watch until the very end.
どんな衣装だと思う？超エッチです。毎回エッチです。
What kind of costume do you think it is? It's super sexy. It's always sexy.
てなわけで何かね、今日はね、メッセージを何か頂いているというのを聞いているんですが、
So, I've heard that I've received some kind of message today...
なんかおやおや？あ！なんとね、あの、あの、あの…知ってますか君たち？あの…
Something's up? Oh! Surprisingly, that, that, that... do you guys know? That...
ほっこりモコモカちゃんからメッセージ頂いてるみたいです。知ってるよね？今日中、知らないなんてことはないよね？モグリだよそれは。
It seems I've received a message from Hokkori Mokomoka-chan. You know them, right? Everyone here, you couldn't possibly not know them, right? You'd be an outsider if you didn't.
あのね、すごく可愛いクマです。見ればわかる。ということで、じゃあメッセージお願いします！
They're a very cute bear. You'll see. So, please, the message!
マリン船長へ
To Captain Marine
デカ！なんだこのお幸せな世界。
Huge! What is this happy world?
こんにちは〜！ほっこりモコモカだよ〜
Hello! I'm Hokkori Mokomoka~
きょうは　だいすきな　マリンせんちょうの　たんじょうび！
Today is my beloved Captain Marine's birthday!
わ〜い！すごい！頭に乗ってるやつちっちゃ！
Yay! Amazing! The one on its head is tiny!
モカもお祝いにきたよ〜！
Moka came to celebrate too~!
わ〜い！お喜びで可愛い！可愛い可愛い、なんか可愛いのがちっちゃ映るやつ…
Yay! It's so happy and cute! Cute, cute, something cute is showing up in that small window...
モカがかざりつけをしたんだ〜
Moka did the decorations!
ああ可愛い！ああすごい！え、凄くない？え、凄い！
Ah, cute! Ah, amazing! Eh, isn't this amazing? Eh, amazing!
いちみのみんな〜！
Everyone in the Ichimi!
いつもがんばっている　マリンせんちょうに　モコモカパワーをいっしょにおくろう！
Let's send the Mokomoka Power together to Captain Marine, who's always working hard!
じゅんびはいいかな？せーのっ　モコモカパワー！
Are you ready? One, two... Mokomoka Power!
可愛い！ブラブラしてる、ブラブラしてる可愛い！
Cute! It's wobbling, wobbling, so cute!
マリンせんちょうの　もとにすてきな　おくりものをしたよ
I've sent a wonderful gift to Captain Marine.
ああ頭のとんがりコーンが落ちそう。
Ah, the pointy cone on its head is about to fall off.
あのひ　モカとであってくれて　ありがとう
Thank you for meeting Moka that day.
これからもモカは　マリンせんちょうのそばにいるよ〜　まったね〜
From now on, Moka will always be by Captain Marine's side. See you later!
贈り物。ありがとうモコモカちゃん。可愛すぎ、可愛すぎ、可愛すぎる！
A gift. Thank you Mokomoka-chan. Too cute, too cute, way too cute!
うわ〜可愛い！船長も今初めて見たんですけど、可愛すぎる！え、有罪マジで可愛すぎる。
Whoa, cute! I'm seeing it for the first time too, and it's too cute! It's a crime, seriously too cute.
じゃちょっと贈り物が来ているってことなんですけど…見て…見て…見て…行くよ〜！じゃ、じゃ、じゃ…これ君たち見える？見えないか。
So, a gift has arrived... let's see... let's see... let's see... Here we go! Now, now, now... can you guys see this? Maybe not.
今船長の元に…わ〜可愛い！ほら帽子被っちゃって！あらあらあら！可愛いわ！ありがとう！ありがとうモカちゃん！可愛いモカちゃん！可愛いわ！
Right now, here with me... whoa, cute! Look, it's wearing the hat! Oh my, oh my! So cute! Thank you! Thank you Moka-chan! Cute Moka-chan! So cute!
暗黒天国 / 作詞：宝野アリカ / 作曲・編曲：片倉三起也
Ankoku Tengoku / Lyrics: Arika Takano / Composition & Arrangement: Mikiya Katakura
Darling 目を開けて
Darling, open your eyes
この世の悪の巣窟で
In this world's nest of evil
吸い玉守る　心を頂戴
Give me your beautiful heart
逃げもできない
You can't even escape
幽閉の蒼白の王子よ
The pale prince of confinement
わたしが女神
I am the goddess
バタフライの羽も
Even the butterfly's wings
わたしの抱擁も
And my embrace too
あなたをまだ見ぬ　極楽へ連れ出せはしない
Won't bring you to the unseen paradise
腐りかけた自由
Decaying freedom
紅にまみれた夢
Red-stained dreams
煉獄の炎で　灼かれたら
If taken to the purgatory flames
再生しめしょう
Let me show you rebirth
冬の夜の空に
In the night sky
色濃い彩
Darkly colored
落ちてゆくなら
Falling together
足掻けあり地獄
Struggle and resist
Darling 声上げて
Darling, raise your voice
このいま刺し違えるほど
To the point of stabbing each other
大事なものが欲しいのなら
If you want something precious
痛みは果てて
Pain will end
奈落で昇天の姫君
In the netherworld, the ascending princess
あなたは…
You are...
怒りの拳も
Even the fist of anger
嘆きの傷も
Even the wounds of grief
跡形もなく
Without a trace
熔けて消えて散って泡沫
Melting, disappearing, scattering like bubbles
すべては密やかに蒼く
Everything turns deeply blue
埋もれた罠に
Buried in traps
ハバタケルノナラ...
If I could take flight...
粉々に砕いてほしいわ
I want you to crush me to pieces
地に堕たぬ病い
An illness that won't fall to the earth
心臓にはポワゾン
A poison in the heart
侵されながらも
While being invaded
一頻り祝福されたし
I have been blessed for a time
泣いたのは嗚咽、紅い砂丘
What cried was a sob, a red sand dune
恋するのは墜とすため
Falling in love is for the sake of falling
毒を食みどのアマイ
Eating poison, which sweet...
あぁ Darling 抱きしめて
Oh Darling, hold me tight
素肌の絹の光沢で
With the luster of the silk of bare skin
恍惚しちゃう時間を頂戴
Give me time to be entranced
あぁ 身体は避けて
Ah, avoid the body
天国での再会の片割れ
The counterpart of a reunion in heaven
あぁ ふたりは迷子
Ah, the two are lost
至極の善と魅惑の奈落
The ultimate good and the enchanting abyss
約束の地は何処か其処か
Where is the promised land, here or there?
夢か現か
Is it a dream or reality?
さぁ 疾く 此処 揺らして
Now, quickly, shake here
全貌を迎えましょう
Let us welcome the whole picture
あぁ Darling 目を開けて
Oh Darling, open your eyes
この世の悪の毒窟も 蝕めない
Even the poisonous den of this world's evil cannot erode it
心を頂戴
Give me your heart
卑下もしない
I won't even humble myself
幽閉の蒼白の王子よ 私が女神
O imprisoned pale prince, I am the goddess
あぁ Darling 声上げて
Oh Darling, raise your voice
このいま刺し違えるほど
So much so that we stab each other right now
大事なものが欲しいのなら
If you want something important
祈りは果てて
Prayers have ended
牢獄で昇天の姫君
O princess ascending in prison
あなたが王
You are the king
組まれた指と懺悔の首と
With clasped fingers and a repentant neck
購う罪は何れか其れか
Which sin is the one to be atoned for?
嘘か真か
Is it a lie or the truth?
アキロゼ先輩〜！
Akirose-senpai~!
よいしょ〜！
Yoisho~!
はあ〜！
Haa~!
一緒に歌うの、これ初めてじゃないですか？
Isn't this the first time we've sung together?
そうだね！何でさ、この曲選んでくれたん？
That's right! Why did you choose this song?
船長の中では、アキロゼ先輩といえば、もうALI PROJECTのイメージなんですよ！
In my mind, Akirose-senpai definitely has an ALI PROJECT image!
あ、そうなんだ！嬉しいな〜！
Oh, is that so! I'm so happy~!
逆に、逆にアキロゼ先輩は...
Conversely, Akirose-senpai...
いいよいいよ、いいリズムだね (笑)
It's fine, it's a good rhythm (laughs)
アキロゼ先輩は、船長と歌うなら、何がいいと思いますか？
Akirose-senpai, if you were to sing with me, what would you like?
マリンちゃんのあの、昭和歌謡とか、めちゃ好きだからな〜。
Since I really like Marin-chan's Showa-era pop songs and stuff.
あ〜！ちょっと昭和系の歌歌いたいんだよね！
Ah! I do want to sing some Showa-style songs!
めちゃめちゃいいじゃないですか！
That sounds great!
あの、キャンディーズとか。
Like Candies.
お、年下の男の子！？
Oh, Toshishita no Otokoko!?
真っ赤なリンゴ、頬ばるリンゴ...
A bright red apple, an apple to munch on...
めっちゃいい！じゃあ次は絶対、「年下の男の子」一緒に歌いましょうね！
That's great! Then next time, let's definitely sing 'Toshishita no Otokoko' together!
いいね！じゃあ次は「年下の男の子」で会いましょう！
Sounds good! Then let's meet next time with 'Toshishita no Otokoko'!
じゃーねー！
See ya!
おめでとねー！
Congratulations!
建前だけの感情論で
With an emotional theory that's just a facade
全てを量ろうなんて
Trying to measure everything
そんなのはお門違い、笑わせないでよね
That's totally wrong, don't make me laugh
だけどたまには楽しいことも
But sometimes, even fun things
必要だと思いの
I think are necessary
気が済むまで私も、満足したいわ
Until I'm satisfied, I want to be fulfilled too
あぁ 目の前から消えていった
Ah, it disappeared from before my eyes
心を刺す嘘みたいに
Like a lie that stabs the heart
ぐるぐるって混ざるような、この感じがたまらない
This feeling of swirling and mixing is irresistible
ねぇ ぶっ飛んじゃうのが良いなら
Hey, if getting blown away is fine
私をもっと本気にさせて
Then make me more serious
逃げるなんて許さないわ
I won't forgive you for running away
やっぱりそんな態度なのね
Just as I thought, that's your attitude
やっぱりそんな態度なのかしら
I wonder if that's really your attitude
甘いのもいいと思うけれど
I think sweet things are good too, but
苦いのも嫌いじゃない
I don't dislike bitter things either
そんな私のことを、わがままだと言うの？
Are you calling me selfish for that?
馬鹿だとかアホらしいとか
Like being a fool or being ridiculous
言いたいだけ言えばいいわ
Just say whatever you want
他人の価値観なんて、私は知らないの
I don't know anything about other people's values
あぁ 掌から落ちていった
Ah, it fell from the palm of my hand
紫色の花みたいに
Like a purple flower
くるくるって踊るような、この感じがたまらない
This feeling of dancing round and round is irresistible
さあ、どうなっちゃうのか
Well, what will happen?
見せてよ
Show me...
本能
your instinct.
どちらが勝つの？
Which one will win?
理性と超絶【自主規制】で
Reason or transcendent [Self-Censorship]
魅せてよ
fascinate me.
本当はここを欲しがるくせに
Even though you actually want this place.
嬉しいとか 気持ちいいとか
Whether it's "happy" or "feels good",
所詮それは自己満足
it's ultimately just self-satisfaction.
戯言を並べ立てて
Lining up nonsensical words...
投げ捨てちゃっていいんじゃない？
Wouldn't it be okay to just throw them away?
思わせて
Make me think so.
もうぶっ飛んじゃったら良いでしょ
It's fine if you just lose your mind already.
一体どこに不満があるの？
Where on earth is the dissatisfaction?
いっそうそうなったら逃がさない
If it comes to that, I won't let you get away.
だからね、ほらね、覚悟して
So, you see, prepare yourself.
さあ、どうなっちゃってもいいから
Now, I don't care what happens,
その目で最後まで見届けて
so watch until the end with those eyes.
どこまで行っても止まらない
No matter how far we go, we won't stop.
だけどね、でもね、そろそろ限界
But, you see, it's almost the limit.
ああもうだめ
Ah, no more.
あああああああ
Ahhhhhhhhh
おお〜〜〜！
Ooooh~~~!
いや、鷹嶺ルイにこの歌はもう本当にぴったりだと思ったんですが
No, I thought this song was a perfect fit for Takane Lui, but...
ガチでぴったりだったわ。
it seriously was a perfect fit.
え、嬉しい嬉しい。
Eh, I'm happy, I'm happy.
いや、でもマリン先輩もめちゃくちゃセクシーで素晴らしかったです。
No, but Marine-senpai was also incredibly sexy and wonderful.
いや、セクシーといえば船長、いや、もう本当にエロ女上司としての立場が
No, speaking of sexy, Senchou... No, really, as a sexy adult woman boss,
危ぶまれてるの、こっち。
my position is being threatened here.
鷹嶺ルイに今、処刑されてる。
I'm being executed by Takane Lui right now.
やだ！
No way!
私セクシーだからなぁ。
Well, I am sexy, after all.
やだ何これスタイル良すぎる！
No, look at this! Your figure is too good!
これじゃマリンがロリータに見えちゃう！
This makes Marine look like a lolita!
いやマリン先輩、元々ロリですからね。
Well Marine-senpai, you were a loli to begin with.
え！？
Eh!?
ロリババアっていう感じで。
Like a "Loli-Babaa" kind of vibe.
マリン。
Marine.
俺だけのババアになれよ。
Become my "Babaa" alone.
おばあちゃんなる...。
I'll become your grandma...
ルイちゃん、メガドライブ買ってあげるね。
Lui-chan, I'll buy you a Mega Drive, okay?
いや、メガドライブはちょっと古い...。
No, Mega Drive is a bit old...
止まらない未来を目指して
Aiming for a future that won't stop,
譲れない願いを抱きしめて
embracing a wish that cannot be yielded.
あああああああああ
Ahhhhhhhhhhh
ゆずれない願い
Unbreakable Wish
海の色が赤く染まってゆく
The color of the sea is being dyed red,
無重力状態
a state of zero gravity.
このまま風にさらわれたい
I want to be swept away by the wind just like this.
いつも飛べないハードルを
The hurdles I can never jump over,
負けない気持ちでクリアしてきたけど
I've cleared them with a spirit that won't give up.
出しきれない実力は
The potential I can't fully bring out,
誰のせい？
whose fault is it?
止まらない未来を目指して
Aiming for a future that won't stop,
譲れない願いを抱きしめて
embracing a wish that cannot be yielded.
色褪せない心の地図
The map of my heart that won't fade,
光にかざそう
let's hold it up to the light.
どれだけ投げれば朝に出会えるの？
How much must I cry out to meet the morning?
孤独な夜
A lonely night.
初めて限界を感じた日
The day I felt my limit for the first time.
きっと恋に落ちるのは
Surely, falling in love is
瞬きみたいな一瞬の情熱だけど
an instantaneous passion like a blink, but...
愛に続く坂道で
On the slope leading to love,
強さを覚えたい
I want to learn strength.
止まらない未来を目指して
Aiming for a future that won't stop,
夢見て
dreaming.
口を閉ざし 瞳を輝かせて
Closing my mouth, making my eyes sparkle,
駆け抜ければ もっと大きな
if I run through, a much bigger...
優しさに出会える
kindness I will meet.
見えたー！
I saw it!
はーい、ということで
Hi, so...
やーも、そらあずというね、この、ほら、主人公的な
Well, with SoraAz, you know, these main-character-like
二人を添えて、バリバリの主題歌歌ってみたかったんですよ！
two by my side, I really wanted to sing a full-on theme song!
めっちゃ楽しかったー！
It was so much fun!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much!
でもなんか、やっぱ二人に挟まれると、船長完全に敵
But somehow, being sandwiched between you two, I feel like a total enemy...
敵なのよ
I'm an enemy.
え、敵じゃないよ？
Eh, not an enemy?
ええー？
What?
なんか敵キャラっぽくない？
Don't I look like an enemy character?
ええー？
Eh?
なんかー
Somehow...
敵ってことは、じゃあ...
If I'm an enemy, then...
敵だね
I'm an enemy.
Enemy, then.
え、どこから出したの？
Wait, where did you get those from?
ちょっと、あの、二人とも戦わないで！
Wait, don't fight, you two!
二人とも戦わないで！待って待って待って！
Don't fight! Wait, wait, wait!
うーうーうー　ららら
Ooh ooh ooh, la la la
ちょっとそこのお嬢さん、愛を買ってみませんか
Hey there, young lady, won't you try buying some love?
月夜に巡り逢った、この縁に
To this fate of meeting on a moonlit night
流し目の瞳、月光照らす金の髪
Sidelong glances, golden hair lit by moonlight
今宵の誰よりも輝いております
You are shining brighter than anyone else tonight
夜な夜な現る、宵闇の怪異の恐怖が
If the fear of the twilight monster that appears night after night
もしもあなたを脅かすならば
should happen to threaten you
さもありながら私、愛の語らいついでに
Then while we're talking of love,
あなたの行く先へお供いたしましょう
I shall accompany you to your destination
嗚呼、嬉しいわ
Ah, I'm so happy
今宵のお相手は貴方？
Are you my partner tonight?
ねぇ、過ごしましょう
Hey, let's spend it together
蠱惑的で幻想的な一夜を
An enchanting and fantastical night
出会いは
The encounter
唐突ながら
was sudden
月明かり
Under the moonlight
の下、惹かれ行く
being drawn in
月夜に飢える
Hungering for the moonlit night
昏い眼をした
With dark eyes
狼の気配は
The presence of a wolf
押し付け
Imposing
がましの愛は
false love
今宵も
Tonight as well
向かう先を探す
searching for where to go
その仮面
Under that mask
の下に気付かれる
being noticed
ことも無いままに
without even being noticed
今宵も
Tonight as well
獲物を求め
seeking prey
冷めぬ夜更けに、外歩くあなた
You, walking outside in the dead of night
そもそもどちらへ、おいででしたか
Where were you going in the first place?
どうぞお気になさらずに、レディの秘密を
Please don't mind me, to uncover a lady's secret
暴くのはあなたに、あるまじき行い
is an improper thing for you to do
では無くって？
Is it not?
透き通る夜こそ 気をつけなければならないさ
夜な夜な現れる シリアルキラーに
In the clear night, you must be careful.
Night after night, the serial killer appears.
月の照らす静寂に 騒ぎ立てる者こそ
霧へと消えれば 夜忍ぶはなくて
In the moonlit silence, those who make a fuss
disappear into the mist, and the night hides nothing.
ああ、イケないよ 殺人鬼を悪戯に
駆り立てる言葉
Ah, it's no good. Words that mischievously
drive the killer.
ねえ、怯え惑う者にこそ
殺人鬼は現れるそうよ
Hey, it seems the killer appears specifically
to those who are trembling in confusion.
出会いは唐突ながら
月明かりの下 惹かれゆく
The encounter is sudden,
but under the moonlight, we are drawn together.
月夜に飢える 昏い瞳をした
狼の気配は 深まる夜のしじまに
Starving for the moonlit night, with dark eyes,
the presence of the wolf deepens in the silence of the night.
霧満ちる 都市の灯の中で
男と女は踊る
In the mist-filled city lights,
man and woman dance,
互いに狙いを定めて
今宵も獲物はそこに
aiming at each other.
Tonight too, the prey is there.
ああ、人影も途絶えた
暗い独り言に 絶望
Ah, where no one else is near.
Despair in a dark monologue.
月を背に 殺人鬼は牙を剥いた
With the moon at their back, the killer bared their fangs.
出会いも唐突ならば
別れも切な 刹那の出来事
If the encounter is sudden,
then the parting is also a sad, momentary event.
月夜に嗤う 紅い瞳をした
狼の姿は
Sneering in the moonlit night, with red eyes,
the wolf's figure is
月を映すナイフを手に
佇むシリアルキラー
standing still with a knife reflecting the moon,
a serial killer.
決して満たされることは無く
やがては再び彷徨う
Never being satisfied,
eventually wandering again.
今宵も獲物は何処に
Tonight too, where is the prey?
よっしゃー！沙花叉に勝った！
Yesss! I beat Sakamata!
ねえ！勝ってないでしょ！
Hey! You didn't win!
いや、船長はね、沙花叉を殺すのが夢だったんだ。
Well, it was the Captain's dream to kill Sakamata.
ねえ、ひどい！掃除屋なのに！
Hey, that's mean! Even though I'm a cleaner!
掃除しちゃいました。
I cleaned you up.
掃除されたんですけど。
I got cleaned, though.
いやー、この曲ね、実は東方のボーカルアレンジの曲なんだけど。
Wow, this song is actually a Touhou vocal arrangement.
もう、マジで歌詞が沙花叉にぴったりなの。
The lyrics really fit Sakamata perfectly.
いやー、ほんと、銀髪とかね。
Yeah, truly, with the silver hair and all.
そうそう、シリアルキラーとかね。
Exactly, and 'serial killer'.
そうそうそう、だから沙花叉が勝つと思ったのに！
Right, right, so I thought Sakamata would win!
ちょっと勝ってみた。
I tried winning for a bit.
ねえ、やだー！でも、めっちゃ良かったです！
Hey, no way! But it was really great!
めっちゃ良かった。
It was really good.
いやー、次こそ絶対マリン先輩に勝ちますからね！
Man, next time I'll definitely beat you, Marine-senpai!
船長の勝ち！勝ち勝ち勝ち勝ち！
Captain's victory! Win win win win!
船長の勝ちじゃない！
It's not Captain's victory!
沙花叉の勝ちー！
Sakamata wins!
胸のピストル鳴らして 焼けに鼓動が邪魔する
Firing the pistol in my chest, my heartbeat is terribly bothersome.
落ち着いてられないそんな情熱
Such passion that I can't stay calm.
解きかけの熱い方程式 次の扉を開いて
A half-solved hot equation, opening the next door.
いけない憧れ時があるよね
There are times when there's a forbidden longing, right?
譲れないその想いに 君が輝くから
Because you shine in that feeling that can't be surrendered.
くじけそうな 今日も平気 成功への 助走は前へ
Even on days when I'm about to give up, I'm okay.
The run-up to success is forward.
Sparking Now! 強くタフなハート
Sparking Now! A strong and tough heart
磨いたら世界は見違える
Once polished, the world will look completely different
Sparking Now! 高くかざしたソウル
Sparking Now! A soul held high
力の限り 目指せ1000%
With all your might, aim for 1000%
もっとずっと遠い場所だと思っていた。手の届かない夢物語。
I thought it was a much more distant place. An unreachable fairy tale.
待て！ねえ待て、父さんでしょ！
Wait! Wait, you're my father, aren't you?!
どんな小さな光も見逃さずにいた。少しでもあなたに近づくために。
I never let even the smallest light escape my sight. All to get even a little closer to you.
この命、たとえ失ってもお守りいたします。
Even if I were to lose this life, I shall protect you.
闇を切り裂く胸の奥の勇気、迷いを断ち切り白い翼。
The courage deep within my chest that slices through the darkness, white wings that cut through hesitation.
もう一人で何でもできるって思うんじゃないわよ！
Don't think you can do everything on your own anymore!
立ち止まりそうになっても、今ここにある笑顔、胸に閉じ込めて。
Even if I'm about to stop, I'll keep the smile that's here now locked in my heart.
守られてるばっかりは嫌やわ。うちも守りたい！
I'm tired of always being protected. I want to protect too!
Burning Heart! 熱く燃やすよ今。
Burning Heart! I'll burn it hot now.
手探りの世界を突き抜けて。
Breaking through this fumbling world.
Burning Heart! 闇を照らしたのは、
Burning Heart! What lit up the darkness was,
自分自身の光る 1000%
My own shining 1000%.
Sparking Now! 強くタフなハート
Sparking Now! A strong and tough heart
磨いたら世界は見違える
Once polished, the world will look completely different
Sparking Now! 高くかざしたソウル
Sparking Now! A soul held high
力の限り 目指せ 1000%
With all your might, aim for 1000%
Burning Heart! 熱く燃やすよ今。
Burning Heart! I'll burn it hot now.
手探りの世界を突き抜けて。
Breaking through this fumbling world.
Burning Heart! 闇を照らしたのは、
Burning Heart! What lit up the darkness was,
自分自身の光る 1000%
My own shining 1000%.
あ～！すいちゃ～い！
Ah~! Suichan~!
すいちゃんと初めて一緒に歌った～！
I sang together with Suichan for the first time~!
嘘だよ！
No way!
いや、今まではね、こう混ざり合っての一緒はあったけど、
Well, up until now, we've sung together in groups,
二人きりでは初めてで。
but this is the first time just the two of us.
初めて。
First time.
え、どう？なんか結構バランスいいんじゃない？
So, how was it? Don't you think the balance was pretty good?
このさ、あ、何？何？
This, like... Oh, what? What?
なんかバランス、色のバランスの話ね。
Like the balance, talking about the color balance.
何が言いたかったかな～？
What was I trying to say~?
え、なんかほら、赤と青でほら、なんかいい感じ...
Like, look, red and blue, it feels like a nice...
なんかちんちくりんだな。
It's kind of puny.
ちょっと待って。
Hold on a second.
なんかすいちゃんの隣に立つとなんか、え、マリン、なんか、
Whenever I stand next to Suichan, Marine, like...
なんだろう、あの、ピクミンみたいだよね。
how do I put it, I look like a Pikmin, right?
赤ピクミン？
Red Pikmin?
え、キャプテン・オリマーの方？赤ピクミンの方？
Wait, the Captain Olimar one? Or the Red Pikmin one?
赤ピクミンの方。あ、キャプテン・オリマーじゃない？
The Red Pikmin one. Wait, not Captain Olimar?
赤ピクミンの方。
The Red Pikmin one.
キャプテン・オリマーじゃない。
Not Captain Olimar.
いや、すいちゃん...
Come on, Suichan...
やめ、そんな話して尺使わないで。
Stop, don't use up the time talking about that.
はい、はい、はい。
Okay, okay, okay.
赤ピクミンしかない。はい。
Nothing but Red Pikmin. Okay.
今日はすいちゃんが選んでくれたこの曲、1000%SPARKING!。
Today, we sang this song Suichan chose, "1000%SPARKING!".
懐かしのアニソン。ネギまの曲なんだよ。知ってた？
An old anime song. It's from Negima. Did you know?
もちろん知ってるよ。
Of course I know.
そうだよね。一緒に歌えて本当に嬉しかった。ありがとう。
Right. I was really happy we could sing it together. Thank you.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
なんかすごかったよね、ネギまあれ。
That Negima arrangement was amazing, wasn't it?
本当に。めっちゃ高かったし。
Truly. It was super high-pitched too.
すいちゃん、踊りも本当にお疲れ様。
Suichan, thanks for the hard work on the dancing too.
お疲れ様！
Good work!
Dan dan 心 Dan dan 熱く
Dan dan heart, dan dan hot
夢いっぱい叶えてみせる
I'll show you I can grant all my dreams
Dan dan 進む Dan dan 弾ける
Dan dan moving forward, dan dan popping
未来をしっかり見て
Look firmly at the future
(ハイハイ進めまだまだいこう)
(Hi hi, move forward, keep going)
(ハイハイ進めほらほらレッツゴー)
(Hi hi, move forward, look look let's go)
大事なことは何だっけ？
What was the important thing again?
(何だっけ？)
(What was it?)
小さな努力が...
A small effort...
...もっとつくるんだ
...making even more.
今を愛してぶつかる
Loving the now and colliding,
(ぶつかる)
(colliding)
そんな勢いでずっと
with that kind of momentum,
一生懸命なんだよ
I'm always giving it my all!
もっと近くで語り合いたいな
I want to talk more closely with you.
頷いた君とどこまで走ろうか
How far shall we run together?
(果てまで)
(To the ends)
走ればいいさ (限界知らない)
We should just keep running. (Knowing no limits)
これからのWonderful Rush みんな
From here on, it's a Wonderful Rush. Everyone,
幸せになるため
in order to become happy,
新しい世界探しにいこうよ
let's go search for a new world.
迷ったらWonderful Rush 僕は
If we get lost, Wonderful Rush. I will
輝きを信じて
believe in the radiance.
遥か遠くの虹だけど
Although it's a rainbow far in the distance,
そうひとつ掴んで
yes, I'll grab hold of one piece.
ダン・ダン・ココロ ダン・ダン・アツク
Dan dan, my heart beats hotter and hotter.
ユメ・イッパイ・カナエテ・ミセル
I'll show you I can make all my dreams come true.
ダン・ダン・ススム ダン・ダン・ハジケル
Dan dan, I move forward, bursting with energy.
人生急に上下左右
Life is suddenly up, down, left, right.
運命的に急展開
A sudden turn of fate.
最低最高最大最新
Lowest, highest, largest, newest.
レッツゴー突進スーパー・ジャンプ
Let's go! Charging forward, Super Jump!
なんでだろうね不思議だよ
I wonder why it's so strange.
楽しいと感じるこの時は
This time when I feel so happy,
瞬間のようで永遠のようだね
feels like a fleeting moment, yet also like eternity.
一緒に飛ぼうよダン・ダン・ダン
Let's fly together, dan dan dan!
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 (そうだ！今が好きで)
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 (That's right! Loving the now)
アン・ナンダ・ブツカル・ン・ダ・ソン・ナ
It was like that, colliding like that,
イキオイ・ツケテ・バトン・ニ・イッショウケンメイ・ダ
gaining momentum and giving my all to the baton!
もっと気持ちを分かり合いたくて
I want to understand each other's feelings more.
隣にいる君いつでも 一緒にいるから一緒がいいね
Since you're always by my side, it's better to be together.
心配いらない (Alright!)
No need to worry! (Alright!)
始まりのWonderful Rush みんな
It's the beginning of a Wonderful Rush. Everyone
好きな場所目指んだ
set out for their favorite place.
巡り合う季節新鮮な景色
Seasons coming together, fresh landscapes.
胸はずむWonderful Rush 僕が
Heart-throbbing Wonderful Rush. What I'm
目指すのは綺麗な 遥か遠くの虹だから
aiming for is a beautiful rainbow far in the distance,
さあ出発だよ
so let's set off!
Wonderful... (My angel... Dream come true)
count 3 2 1 0
ハイハイ・スーパー・ジャンプ
Hai hai, Super Jump!
オーイェー・スーパー・ジャンプ
Oh yeah, Super Jump!
ラッキー・ワンダー・まだまだ・レッツゴー
Lucky wonder, we're still going, let's go!
もっと近くで語り合いたいな
I want to talk more closely with you.
頷いた君とどこまで走ろうか 果てまで走ればいいさ
How far shall we run together? We should just keep running to the end.
限界それなに？ (Alright!)
Limits? What's that? (Alright!)
これからのWonderful Rush みんな
From here on, it's a Wonderful Rush. Everyone
幸せになるため 新しい世界探しにいこうよ
in order to become happy, let's go search for a new world.
迷ったらWonderful Rush 僕は
If we get lost, Wonderful Rush. I will
輝きを信じて 遥か遠くの虹だけど
believe in the radiance. Although it's a rainbow far in the distance,
胸はずむWonderful Rush
Heart-throbbing Wonderful Rush.
僕らが目指すのは綺麗な
What we're aiming for is a beautiful,
遥か遠くの虹だから
rainbow far in the distance,
さあ出発だよ
so let's set off!
ダン・ダン・ココロ ダン・ダン・アツク
Dan dan, my heart beats hotter and hotter.
ユメ・イッパイ・カナエテ・ミセル
I'll show you I can make all my dreams come true.
ダン・ダン・ススム ダン・ダン・ハジケル 未来をしっかり見て
Dan dan, I move forward, bursting with energy. Take a good look at the future!
せーの！マリン、お誕生日おめでとう！
One, two! Marine, happy birthday!
みんな...ありがとう...
Everyone... thank you...
あれ？ちょっと待って。いつものマリンがいない。
Huh? Wait a second. The usual Marine isn't here.
え、ほんとだ。あれ、マリンどこ？
Oh, you're right. Huh, where's Marine?
お前誰だ？
Who are you?
マリンじゃなくね？マリン？
That's not Marine, right? Marine?
君は誰？
Who are you?
じゃじゃーん！
Ta-da!
なんだ？なんかセクシーお姉さん来たぺこだけど。
What's this? Some kind of sexy lady has arrived-peko.
そうなんです。誕生日ということで、何歳になったと思う？
That's right. Since it's my birthday, how old do you think I've become?
そう、17歳。さ、4...4周目。
That's right, 17 years old. The... 4th round.
合計17の...
A total of 17...
待って。17歳4周目×4ってこと？
Wait. 17 years old, 4th round times 4?
やばいぞ、それ。
That's dangerous.
だから、今回の衣装はちゃんとね、成長したマリンということで。
So, this outfit is indeed a 'grown-up' Marine.
ちょっと年を取ってみました。
I tried aging a bit.
勇気を出して、勇気の決断、年を取るという決断をしました。
I took a leap of faith, a courageous decision to age.
めっちゃエロくね？
Isn't it super erotic?
大丈夫なのこれ？
Is this even allowed?
おっぱいがすごい！
Her boobs are amazing!
じゃんじゃーん！
Ta-da!
はい、こちらの衣装ね、100万人記念でいただきました。
Yes, I received this outfit for reaching 1 million subs.
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
ありがとうございます！じゃんじゃかじゃーん！
Thank you very much! Ta-da-da-da!
え、おっぱいがすごい... 大丈夫？
Wait, those boobs are incredible... Are you okay?
めっちゃ揺れてる！やばいよこれ！
They're swaying so much! This is crazy!
え、なんのこと？
Eh, what are you talking about?
めっちゃ動く！すごい！
They move so much! Incredible!
すっごい揺れてるぺこ！
They're swaying like crazy, peko!
いや、目の前に来たから出しちゃおっかなって。
Well, they're right there, so I thought I'd show them.
手とかあるし、手。あ、船長...
There's hands and stuff, hands. Oh, the Captain's...
あ、毎回あかさあい先生、船長のお母さんですね。
Ah, every time Akasa Ai-sensei—my 'mother.'
毎回「エッチな感じでお願いします」って丸投げしてるんですけど...
I always just tell her 'make it erotic' and leave it to her...
そしたら、こうなりました。
...and this is what happened.
めっちゃええやん。
It's really nice.
いいねいいね。
I like it, I like it.
え、髪の毛も可愛いね。
Oh, your hair is cute too.
そうなの、髪の毛も。ほら、ほら。
That's right, the hair too. Look, look.
こんな、メッシュ入ってるし。
It's got these highlights and everything.
え、もうみんなもしかしてさ、これ脱いでほしい？
Wait, maybe you all want me to take this off?
え、大丈夫？
Eh, is that okay?
なんかそろそろ帰るか。
Well, it's about time to head home.
帰ろうか、時間だもんね。
Let's go back, it's almost time.
バイバイ！お疲れ様ー！
Bye-bye! Good work everyone!
脱いだところ見たい？みんな、脱いだところ見たい？
You want to see me take it off? Do you all want to see?
誰も... あれ？
No one...? Huh?
海賊ならヨーホー
If you're a pirate, Yo-ho
お宝掲げヨーホー
Raise the treasure, Yo-ho
さあ、今、旗の下、集え
Now, gather under the flag
方舟描いてくだ...
Draw an ark...
出航！
Set sail!
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
踊るアホイ 見るアホイ
Dancing Ahoy, Watching Ahoy
全速前進だー！
Full speed ahead!
Ahoy!! 我ら宝鐘海賊団☆
作詞：まろん(IOSYS) 作曲：ARM(IOSYS)
Ahoy!! We are the Houshou Pirates☆
Lyrics: maron (IOSYS) Composition: ARM (IOSYS)
爪 詰め 大洋は燦々 絶好海日和だ
Pack your gear, the ocean is bright, it's a perfect day for sailing
歌え 唄え 最高の本性 波の音に乗せ
Sing, sing your true self, riding the sound of the waves
どんぶらこ 海で さあ 行く先 おかげアニキがハッピー
Floating on the sea, let's go, thanks to you all everyone is happy
踊らな損々 ギラギラ
If you don't dance it's your loss, glittering
野望 ボロボロ マイハウスで 夢を見て
Ambition in tatters, dreaming in my house
あぁ... 神様 いつかこのマリンを本物の海賊にしてください
Ah... God, please make this Marine a real pirate someday
声を上げて さあ 出航だ 我ら宝鐘海賊団☆
Raise your voice, now set sail, we are the Houshou Pirates☆
コンパス片手に 旗を上げ この海をジャックしちゃおう
Compass in hand, raise the flag, let's take over this sea
よそ見して おいで 共にヨーホーヨーホー叫ぼう
Don't look away, come, let's shout Yo-ho, Yo-ho together
あぁ... 最高の 日々 ようこそ 我が船
Ah... the best days, welcome to my ship
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
踊るアホイ 見るアホイ
Dancing Ahoy, Watching Ahoy
1, 2, 3, サバ！サバ！
1, 2, 3, Mackerel! Mackerel!
熱く語ろうよ パッション 思いを解き放て
Let's talk passionately, release your feelings
熱く きらめく ファッション 形から入るタイプです
Hot, glittering fashion, I'm the type who starts with appearances
発射 10秒前 走れ ガソリン入れちゃ
10 seconds to launch, run, fill up the tank
日焼けも照れるわ ギラギラ
Sunburn is embarrassing too, glittering
じわり汗も 滴るイイ女 だけど
I'm a fine woman even with sweat dripping, but
あぁ... 神様 船長がセンシティブだと BANされちゃうのですね はにゃ〜
Ah... God, if the captain is too sensitive, she'll get banned, won't she? Hannya~
歌えばほら 取り戻せ それが宝鐘海賊団☆
Look, if you sing, you'll get it back, that's the Houshou Pirates☆
君たちとなら たどり着ける 伝説のエルドラド
With you all, we can reach the legendary El Dorado
よそ見 楽しけりゃ 歌えヨーホーヨーホー足りない
If you're having fun looking elsewhere, sing Yo-ho, Yo-ho, it's not enough
あぁ... この景色 大切な仲間よ
Ah... this scenery, my precious comrades
宴だ 宴だ 騒げや 騒げ
It's a party, it's a party, let's make some noise
踊るアホイ 見るアホイ
Dancing Ahoy, Watching Ahoy
同じアホなら 飲まなきゃ損々
If you're the same fool, it's a loss if you don't drink
ジョッキ片手に 行きますよ
With a mug in hand, here I go
アホイ！アホイ！アホイ！アホイ！
Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy! Ahoy!
宝鐘マリン 宝鐘マリン 世界で一番可愛いよ
Houshou Marine, Houshou Marine, you're the cutest in the world
メスガキ メスガキ エロガキ エロガキ
Mesugaki, Mesugaki, Erogaki, Erogaki
ボインパフ ボインパフ お嬢さん パンツは何色？
Boing-puff, Boing-puff, young lady, what color are your panties?
お宝 お宝 面舵 面舵
Treasure, treasure, hard-a-starboard, hard-a-starboard
撫で回すぞ 見てみたい
I'm gonna stroke it, I want to see
アハンアハン もっともっと
A-han A-han, more more
セクシーに もっともっと
Sexy, more more
いやんまいっちんぐ もっともっと
Oh no, matching, more more
もっと！もっと！もっと！
More! More! More!
(ダッシュ！)
(Dash!)
もっと！もっと！もっと！
More! More! More!
(ゼビセブ！)
(Sebisebu!)
もっと！もっと！もっと！
More! More! More!
(前へ！)
(Forward!)
もっと！もっと！もっと！
More! More! More!
(出会って5秒で！)
(Out in 5 seconds!)
爆速パ〜ン！
Full speed bang!
はぁはぁ... 船長は君たちをそんな子に育てた覚えはありません。
Huff, huff... I don't remember raising you all to be like that.
本当に！ ねえ、だぞ。
Seriously! Hey, I mean it.
立てば痴女、座れば昭和、歩く姿はTバック...
Pervert when standing, Showa-era when sitting, wearing a thong when walking...
夢を詰め込み　この船で　後悔なんて　させない
Filling our dreams on this ship, I won't let you have any regrets.
君たちの　おかげで私は　船長に　なれるから
Because of all of you, I can be the Captain.
向こう一軒家となりの
Next door to that house,
撃て〜！
Fire~!
声を上げて　出航だ
Raise your voice, it's time to set sail!
我ら宝鐘海賊団
We are the Houshou Pirates!
コンパス片手に　旗を上げ
Compass in hand, raise the flag!
この海を　ジャックしちゃおう
Let's hijack this sea!
夜な夜な　ついておいで　ともに　ヨーホーヨーホー叫ぼう
Follow me night after night, let's shout "Yo-ho, yo-ho" together!
さあ最高な日々　ようこそ
Now, to these wonderful days, welcome.
わたくし　宝鐘　宝鐘　宝鐘　海賊団
To my ship, the Houshou, Houshou, Houshou Pirates!
それではいきますよ！
Here we go!
出航〜〜！！
Set sail~~!!
宝鐘マリン オリジナル楽曲 第四弾
Houshou Marine's 4th Original Song
I'm Your Treasure Box
*あなたはマリンせんちょうを たからばこからみつけた。
*You found Captain Marine from a treasure box.
Sexy 世界一 スーパーピチピチ
Sexy, world's best, super lively,
ぶっちゃけ船長 捕まえたくない？
Honestly, don't you want to catch the Captain?
やばな Get Treasure Maybe Destiny
Dangerous, get treasure, maybe destiny,
私の甘さが 欲しいでしょ
You want my sweetness, right?
(Ah-ha!)
秘宝の扉を
The door to the hidden treasure,
優しくたたいて
Knock on it gently,
ほのかの扉を
The door of faint fragrance,
マジで早く開けて
Seriously, open it quickly!
このあと22時プレミア公開
Premiere at 22:00 tonight
魅惑を 隠す箱
A box that hides enchantment,
秘宝に 香る危なげな
A dangerous scent wafting from the treasure,
Dangerous Marine Smell
これ開けたら君たちになんて言ってあげるべきかな？
I wonder what I should say to you all when you open this?
探してたのは船長？ それとも...
Was it the Captain you were looking for? Or...
ああ、そんなにくっついちゃダメだぞ。
Ah, don't get so close to me.
ほら、お宝の魅力にピンときて見つけちゃった。
Look, you found it, attracted by the charm of the treasure.
いいじゃない。
Isn't it nice?
妥当だ ネットの赤
Appropriate, the red of the internet,
極上の 海賊の秘宝
The finest pirate treasure,
それは私
That would be me.
甘く 漂う
Sweetly drifting,
香りを どうか 変わらないで
Please don't let the scent change,
あけてみて
Try opening it.
Sexy 世界一 スーパーピチピチ
Sexy, world's best, super lively,
ぶっちゃけ船長 捕まえたくない？
Honestly, don't you want to catch the Captain?
やばな Get Treasure Maybe Destiny
Dangerous, get treasure, maybe destiny,
私の甘さが 欲しいでしょ
You want my sweetness, right?
(Ah-ha!)
秘宝の扉を
The door to the hidden treasure,
優しくたたいて
Knock on it gently,
ほのかの扉を
The door of faint fragrance,
マジで早く開けて
Seriously, open it quickly!
司令塔 あなたの手
The control tower, your hand,
回数にこぼす 甘いため息の鍵
The key to the sweet sighs spilled countless times,
純真なバラが
A pure rose...
揺れる Marine
Sways, Marine,
Release 魂
Release your soul,
七つの大海を
Over the seven seas,
Summer Breeze
また駆け進め
Keep running again,
Summer Snow Marine
まだ誰からも 何 想像してんの
Still from no one... What are you imagining?
Now please touch Marine's deep
Open a treasure box
Open the primary
Oh I whisper
いなごも黙る　なりのサスペンス
A suspense that would even silence locusts
君たちも　もう我慢できないっすな
You guys can't hold back anymore, can you?
野暮な女言わせちゃ　Maybe dance for me
Don't make me say it, maybe dance for me
私のすべてを　手に入れて
Take all of me
ぴたっ　止まる
Suddenly, I stop
ハッとするでしょ
It catches you off guard, doesn't it?
ぱっと目が合う
Our eyes meet in a flash
誰か助けて
Someone, help me
マジでえっちすぎ
Seriously, this is way too lewd
君たち　なにかんがえてんの？
Guys, what are you thinking about?
分かってるのは　私を
All I know is you're...
だから　今すぐ　暴いてよ
So, expose me right now
だから　バコッ
So, pop it open
あなたの　祭りだね　と
Saying it's your festival
君たち　開けてー
Everyone, open it up!
はい、君たちいかがでしたでしょうか？
So, everyone, how did you like that?
お誕生日お祝いしてくれてサンキュー！
Thank you for celebrating my birthday!
今日お披露目しました「I'm Your Treasure Box　あなたはマリン船長を宝箱から見つけた」
Today I premiered "I'm Your Treasure Box: You Found Captain Marine in a Treasure Box."
ミュージックビデオこの後22時からプレミアム公開です。
The music video will have its premiere after this at 10 PM.
24時から各種音楽サイトにて配信開始ですよ。
It'll be available on music streaming sites from midnight.
ミュージックビデオも曲もえっちになってます。
Both the MV and the song are quite lewd.
さあ、そして今年もグッズ出させていただきますよ。
And now, I'll be releasing merch this year as well.
「あー、買わなきゃよかった」と思わないよう、ここは思い切って是非ともご購入ください。
Don't regret it later—take the plunge and buy them now!
まずはこちら、B2タペストリーです。
First up is this B2 tapestry.
今回の新衣装で、船長の母、あかさあい先生描き下ろしです。
It's a new illustration by Akasa Ai-sensei, my creator, in my new outfit.
年々ドロンジョ様然としていくマリンの情味たっぷらなイラストになっています。
It captures Marine's charm as she becomes more like Doronjo every year.
これでいつでも見下ろされて気持ちよくなれる。
Now you can feel good being looked down upon anytime.
続いてこちら、一味Tシャツです。
Next is the Ichimi T-shirt.
マリンとお揃いパーカーは夏場はやはり暑いので...
Since the hoodie matching mine is too hot for summer...
この海賊然としたボーダーシャツでアドを獲ろう。
Get an advantage with this pirate-style striped shirt.
船長のシンボルマークも入っていて、ただのボーダーシャツとは訳が違う。
It has my symbol, so it's not just any striped shirt.
外で着るのが恥ずかしい？
Too embarrassed to wear it outside?
そんな時は身内でウォーリーを探せごっこすることも可能です。
Then you can just play "Where's Waldo?" with your family.
そしてこちらは船長が書きました、ラバーストラップです。
And these are rubber straps illustrated by me!
不人気な絵柄があるとショックするので、ランダムにしました。
I'd be shocked if any were unpopular, so it's a random selection.
何が出ても必ず喜んでください。
Be happy with whichever one you get!
そしてそしてこちら、航海日誌風手帳。
And finally, this logbook-style notebook.
大人の男が使ってもイケてるし、メスも優勝確定のおしゃれ手帳。
It's cool for men and definitely a win for the ladies. Very stylish.
船長の帽子のキーホルダーみたいなのも付いてます。
It even comes with a keychain shaped like my hat.
はい、そして今回もフルセットございます。
And yes, we have a full set available again.
全てまとめてご購入いただきましたらば...
If you purchase the whole set...
数量限定、直筆メッセージ入りポストカードと...
You'll get a limited-edition postcard with a handwritten message...
生誕祭前日をイメージしたマリンと君のラブラブシチュエーションボイスをプレゼントします。
And a romantic situation voice pack of you and me the day before the live.
数量限定が売り切れましたらば、複製メッセージ＆サイン入りポストカードになります。
Once the limited set sells out, it'll be a printed message and signature.
こちらもね、船長がぎっしりと、思いを込めてメッセージ書いたので...
I filled those with a lot of thought and messages too...
まあこれはこれで嬉しいみたいなところがある。
So those are pretty great in their own right.
ということで、宝鐘マリン誕生日記念グッズ2022...
So, the Houshou Marine Birthday Commemorative Goods 2022...
22時から販売開始です。
Sales start at 10 PM.
Twitterや概要欄のURLをチェックお願いします。
Please check the link in the description or on Twitter.
あ、それから船長のfigmaも7月29日から受注開始していますので...
Oh, and pre-orders for my figma also started on July 29th...
是非ともゲットしてくださいね。
So make sure to grab one!
そして、何やらホロライブサマーから告知が少しだけあるようです。
And now, it seems there's a little announcement from Hololive Summer.
今からお知らせいたしますよ。
Let's take a look.
私が... やらなくちゃ。
I... have to do it.
君たち、今の見ましたか？
Did you guys see that just now?
ということでなんと、ホロライブ・サマー2022本日より開始します！
Hololive Summer 2022 starts today!
いやサマーといえば船長、もう2年近く、2年か、2年くらい本当にね、脱ぎたいという思いでやってきたんですけども...
Speaking of summer, I've spent nearly two years wanting to show more skin...
やだもー、ね、キミたち落ち着いて。脱ぐのが全てじゃない。
Oh stop it, you guys, calm down. Taking clothes off isn't everything.
サマーって色々あるから。え？
There's a lot to summer. Eh?
まあキミたちどうせ水着だと思ってるんでしょうけど
Well, you guys probably think it's all about swimsuits anyway.
わかんないからね。まだわかんないから。
But you don't know yet. You don't know for sure.
水着…んー…あー…
Swimsuits... hmm... ah...
もう聞かないで。やめて。引きずり出さないで、
Don't ask anymore. Stop. Don't try to drag it out of me,
船長から情報を引きずり出そうとしないで。
don't try to drag information out of the Captain.
や、でもね、もう本当に、これ船長が勝手に宣言してるんじゃなくて、
But really, it's not just the Captain making this declaration on her own,
これは公式からね、あの、言われて宣言してるんで、
this is being declared because I was told to by the official side,
もうこれは船長が勝手にやってるんじゃなく、
so this isn't just the Captain acting on her own,
本当に公式で全体で盛り上げていくホロライブサマーとなっております。
it's Hololive Summer that the whole official team is going to hype up together.
ということでね、この配信のあとに、
So, after this stream,
公式サイトとティザー、あ、ここに、はい、ご覧ください。
the official site and teaser—oh, here, please take a look.
え、この配信のあとに公式サイトとティザームービーのフルバージョンが公開予定です！
Um, after this stream, the official site and the full version of the teaser movie are scheduled to be released!
詳細はホロライブ公式ツイートをお待ちください。
Please wait for the official Hololive tweet for details.
よし、じゃあちょっとホロライブサマーに向けて、よし、アップしてくか。いきます。出航ー！
Alright then, let's get warmed up for Hololive Summer. Here we go. Setting sail!
バイバーイ！
Bye bye!
キミたち～♡
You guys~♡
生誕祭見てくれてありがとう♡
Thank you for watching the birthday celebration♡
キミたちが力をくれるおかげでやりたいことや夢をかなえられてますが
Thanks to the strength you give me, I'm able to fulfill my dreams and things I want to do,
キミたちに愛されてると、体内からドパドパドパミんが出て若返るワー♡
being loved by you guys makes dopamine gush out from inside me and I feel younger~♡
これからも愛してね♡
Please keep loving me♡
マリンの若さのために。
For Marine's youth.